http://www.plagiarismchecker.com/privacy.php

Free Plagiarism Detection On the Internet
Check a Document :
Check a Web Page NEW! :
Handouts :
Report Plagiarism :
PlagiarismChecker.com Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices for www.plagiarismchecker.com, its applications, products, software various related services (together referred to as the "Services"). The Services are provided by PlagiarismChecker.com and its parent, affiliates, business divisions and subsidiaries (referred to as "us" or "we"). We are committed to protecting your privacy online. Please read the information below to learn the following regarding your use of the Services.
You agree that this Privacy Policy is part of our Terms of Service for www.plagiarismchecker.com, and by accessing or using our Services, you agree to be bound by all of its terms and conditions. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not access or use the Services.
1. Changes to the Policy.
We may change this Privacy Policy at any time. We made provide notice of such changes issuing an e-mail to the e-mail address listed by registered users and/or by posting a notice about our revised Privacy Policy on the Services. You agree to assume the responsibility to (a) visit this page periodically to review any such changes and to (b) maintain a valid e-mail address as a registered user. By accessing and continuing to use the Services after we post notice of any changes, you signify your consent and agreement to the updated Privacy Policy.
2. Types of Information Collected
In order to better provide you with our numerous services, we collect information from our users.
We collect Personally Identifiable Information, which is information that lets us know the specifics of who you are. When you engage in certain activities on the Services, such as registering for a membership, ordering a product or service, submitting content and/or posting content in discussion forums or other public areas, entering a contest or sweepstakes, filling out a survey, or sending us feedback, we may ask you to provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form. Providing information is purely optional on your part; however, not all features and services (such as, responding to your inquiries) would be available to you if you elect not to provide information. The information we may request include your name, address, e-mail address and other information. When ordering our Services, you may be asked to provide a credit card number or other payment information. Depending upon the activity, some of the information we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory data with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity.
We also collect Non-Personally Identifiable information that does not by itself identify a specific individual. We gather certain information about you based upon where you use the Services in several ways. This information is compiled and analyzed on both a personal and an aggregated basis. This information may include the Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") that you just came from, which URL you next go to, what browser you are using, and/or your Internet Protocol ("IP") address.
3. Collection Methods and Use of Information
We do not collect any Personally Identifiable Information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us. You provide certain Personally Identifiable Information to us when you (a) register for the Services and give us your e-mail address with us; (b) sign up for special offers from selected third parties; (c) send e-mail messages, submit forms, or transmit other information by telephone or letter; (d) interact with our Services and advertisements; (e) transact with us, such as, when you make purchases, submit payment information, respond to any offers, or download applications from us; and (f) provide us with information when you contact us for help.
In addition, we may also collect, or our third-party ad server and/or content server may collect, certain Non-Personally Identifiable Information. This information is ultimately stored in the form of store categories, and, in some cases, specific URLs. We use your IP address to diagnose problems with our servers, software, to administer our Services, and to gather demographic information. Our third-party ad servers will also provide us reports that will tell us how many ads were presented and clicked upon on our Services in a manner that does not identify personally any individual.
We may use third-party analytics service to collect, monitor and analyze the information collected as described above.
We will primarily use your Personally Identifiable Information to provide our services to you, fulfill any transactions, enhance the operation of our Services, fill orders, improve our marketing and promotional efforts, statistically analyze use of the Services, improve our product and service offerings, provide you with updates about our products and services, provide support, send you notices about our Privacy Policy and Terms of Service, enforce our terms, and to provide offers from our affiliates and from third parties that may be of interest to you.
4. Release of Information
We do not sell, trade, or rent your Personally Identifiable Information to others. We do provide some of the Services through contractual arrangements with affiliates, services providers, partners, and other third parties. We and our service partners use your Personally Identifiable Information to operate our Services and to deliver their services. For example, we must release your credit card information to the card-issuing bank to confirm payment for products and services purchased from us; release your address information to the delivery service to deliver products that you ordered; and provide order information to third parties that help us provide customer service.
If such service providers have access to Personally Identifiable Information, they are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy.
Occasionally, we may be required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide Personally Identifiable Information to the appropriate governmental authorities. We will disclose Personally Identifiable Information upon receipt of a court order or subpoena or to cooperate with a law enforcement investigation. We fully cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our services for illegal activities. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful.
We may also provide Non-Personally Identifiable Information about our customers' sales, traffic patterns, and related Services information to third-party advertisers, but these statistics do not include any Personally Identifiable Information.
5. Updating and Correcting Information
We believe you should have the ability to access and edit the Personally Identifiable Information that you have provided to us. You may change any of your Personally Identifiable Information in your account online at any time by linking to your account in accordance with instructions posted elsewhere on the Services. You may also access and correct your personal information and privacy preferences by contacting us at:
.
Please include your name, address, and/or e-mail address when you contact us.
We encourage you to promptly update your Personally Identifiable Information if it changes. You may ask to have the information on your account deleted or removed; however, because we keep track of past transactions, you cannot delete information associated with past transactions on the Services. In addition, it may be impossible to completely delete your information without some residual information because of backups.
6. User Choices on Collection and Use of Information
We may, from time to time, send you e-mail regarding our products and services and third party products and services that may be of interest to you. You will have the opportunity to opt out of any further mailings at any time. Or, at any time, you can easily edit your account information to no longer receive such offers and mailings.
You also have choices with respect to cookies, as described below. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. If you choose to reject all cookies, some parts of our Services may not work properly.
7. Use of Cookies
Cookies are a standard Internet technology, and many major web Services use them to provide useful features for their members. We use cookies to allow us to improve the quality of our service, store user preferences, store and retrieve login information on a user's system, and to personalize content and offers of interest to our users. We also allow our service providers to collect non-personally identifiable information by placing cookies on the Services that will track certain performance of our services, such as, web traffic, click-throughs, etc., in order to assist us and our service providers in better understanding the interests of our users and to better serve those interests. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you'd prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies. However, you may not be able to take full advantage of the Services if you do so.
8. Advertising
Advertisements that may appear on the Services are delivered to users by our advertisers. We and our advertisers may from time-to-time use advertising network providers, including our own network services and third party networks, to help present advertisements on the Services and other Web services. These advertisers and ad networks use cookies, web beacons or similar technologies on your browser to help present offers, better target and measure the effectiveness of their advertisements by using data gathered on an anonymous basis over time and across their network of Web pages to determine the preference of their audiences. These cookies and web beacons do not collect any personal information from your computer, such as your e-mail address. The use of cookies and web beacons by advertisers and ad networks is subject to their own privacy policies.
9. Links and Other Services
This Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. We may present links in a format that enables us to keep track of whether these links have been followed. We use this information to improve the quality of our search technology, customized content and advertising. This Privacy Policy applies to the Services that are owned and provided by us. We are not responsible for the privacy policies, practices or contents of any third party web services. Please refer to the privacy policies of such third party web sites for information on what kinds of personally identifiable information such web sites collect and their respective privacy practices, terms, and conditions.
10. Acquisition
We reserve the right to transfer your personal information in the event of a transfer of ownership of PlagiarismChecker.com or PlagiarismChecker.com, such as acquisition by or merger with another company. If an acquiring company should plan to materially change this privacy policy, we will notify you beforehand.
11. Security
We take steps to help protect your personal information. We require password protection physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect personal information about you. We limit access to personal information about you to employees and authorized who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. Please remember that no technological environment is completely secure and we cannot guarantee the confidentiality of any communication or material transmitted or posted on the Services or any other web services over the Internet. If you have any other questions about the security of our Services, please contact us at .
12. Miscellaneous Privacy Issues
Our policy is that we do not knowingly collect, use, or disclose Personally Identifiable Information about visitors that are under 13 years of age.
You should also be aware that when Personally Identifiable Information is voluntarily disclosed (i.e. your name, e-mail address, etc.) in the discussion forums or other public areas on the Services, that information, along with any information disclosed in your communication, can be collected and used by third parties and may result in unsolicited messages from third parties. Such activities are beyond our control and this Policy does not apply to such information. Any submissions to chat rooms or other public areas on the Services are accepted with the understanding that they are accessible to all third parties. If you do not want your comments to be viewed by third parties, you are advised not to make any submissions. Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your password and/or account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you are online.
13. California Users.
If you are a California resident, in addition to the rights set forth above, you have the right to request information from us regarding the manner in which we share certain categories of your personal information with third parties, for the third parties' direct marketing purposes. California law provides that you have the right to submit a request to us at the designated address and receive the following information:
the categories of information we disclosed to third parties for the third parties direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year
the names and addresses of third parties that received such information, and
if the nature of a third party's business cannot be reasonably determined from the third party's name, examples of the products or services marketed.
You are entitled to receive a copy of this information in a standardized format and the information will not be specific to you individually. Our designated email address for such requests is .
Last Updated: 14 April 2012
Printable Versions of the Handouts
Handouts
Copying From the Web
Is Plagiarism Illegal?
This site directs users to Google and Yahoo! search results but is is in no way endorsed by those companies.
Google™ is a trademark of Google, Inc.
Yahoo!™ is a trademark of Yahoo! Inc.
Do not make automated search queries using this site.
You will be permanently blocked if this happens.
The material on this site is Copyright © 2005 - 2020PlagiarismChecker.com.
